# **Thomas J Lazore**

Software Developer

Address Savannah, GA, 31410

**Phone** 315-778-6632

E-mail tomlazore@gmail.com

Full stack software developer certified from Georgia Tech. Experience working with technologies such as JavaScript, Express, and MongoDB in the development of group and solo projects. A background as a paramedic has sharpened skills to be an effective team member as well as resourceful independent worker.

### **Projects**

#### Never Alone | github.com/tlaze/NeverAlone

- Live Application: never-alone-platform.herokuapp.com/
- **Description:** Team of 4 members developing a social media website geared towards mental health. This project had a 50 person user base. Each were able to create personal profiles and add unique posts/comments.
- **Responsibilities:** Creating, editing, and deleting posts | Mobile Responsiveness.
- Technology Used: Bootstrap|Javascript|Node|Express|Handlebars|Express-Session|MySQL2|Sequelize|bcrypt|Heroku|Nodemailer

#### Tech Blog | github.com/tlaze/tech-blog

- Live Application: cryptic-thicket-49114.herokuapp.com/
- **Description:** Forum based application for creating posts, updating, and deleting posts.
- Technology Used: Bootstrap|Javascript|Node|Express|Handlebars|Express-Session|MySQL2|Sequelize|bcrypt|Heroku

#### Weather Dashboard | github.com/tlaze/weather-dashboard

- Live Application: tlaze.github.io/weather-dashboard/
- **Description:** Fetches data from a third party API to display current and future weather conditions for cities that users enter.
- **Technology Used:** HTML|CSS|Bootstrap|Javascript|JQuery|OpenWeatherOneAPI|Local Storage

#### **Education**

2021-12

## 2021-09 - Full Stack Coding Boot Camp

Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta, GA

#### 2018-09 - Computer Science

**2019-09** Monroe Community College - Rochester, NY

- Relevant Coursework Completed: Intro to Computer Science with Java & Programming with Python
- Completed a summer internship with Rochester Institute of Technology working on the front-end development of an application that recognizes handwritten mathematical formulas and converts it into searchable queries.

## **Work History**

2019-08

## 2017-09 - Paramedic 2020-03

Irondequoit Ambulance, Irondequoit, NY

- Triaged injuries by communicating with patients, bystanders and family members, and identified appropriate medical facility for transport.
- Used EMSCharts to accurately document services provided to reduce liability and improve patient

## 2019-05 - Research Assistant Intern

Rochester Institute Of Technology, Rochester, NY

- Presented technical research results to diverse audiences through written, visual and oral media.
- https://www.cs.rit.edu/~dprl/mathseer/